govtribe.com 2019-09-24

# GovTribe Privacy Policy | GovTribe Help Center

This privacy policy has been compiled to address GovTribe’s use and protection of the personal data, company data, work product, and information related to business development and market research (“Content”) that GovTribe users store on GovTribe in the course of using GovTribe’s website and associated services (“Services”). Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Content in accordance with our Services. For more information on our Services, and the ways in which they can be used, please review our [Terms of Use](https://help.govtribe.com/terms-and-conditions/govtribe-terms-of-use).

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, credit card information, basic company information or other details to help you with your experience.

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.  

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, browse and use the Services, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

Your Content is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

We have in place mechanisms to monitor our systems for malware and attempted data breaches.

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember a search query you initiated so we can preserve it as you browse other pages on the site. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

####  In summary, we use cookies to:

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

 You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Chrome) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

####  If users disable cookies in their browser:

If you disable cookies off, some website features will be disabled. It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our Services will not function properly. We use cookies to retain your session information, browsing history on GovTribe, login information, and other basic information to provide you with a seamless user experience.  

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information (PII) or your Content. We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. We, along with third-party vendors such as Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) to track aggregate user activity and internal site usage metrics in order to improve site usability.

Your Content, but not your billing information, is automatically shared with all other individuals on your GovTribe account, only. If you are on a Standard or Premium account as either the account owner or an account member, any Content you add to or create in the course of using our Services is viewable and accessible by the other users on that same account. This is the intended purpose of our Services – the collaboration between account members on Content. 

Neither your Content, your PII, nor your billing information is viewable or accessible by any other GovTribe users outside of your account. GovTribe will not share any of this information with any other individuals or organizations, whether they are GovTribe users or not. Please also refer to our [Terms of Use](https://help.govtribe.com/terms-and-conditions/govtribe-terms-of-use) for more information regarding how GovTribe handles your Content.

The only action that you can take on GovTribe that would result in external GovTribe users seeing any information you create is to “Claim” your Vendor profile. Again, the intended purpose Vendor profile Claiming is to market your business to GovTribe users outside of your account. 

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

####  According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
  * Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page
  * Users are able to change their personal information by logging in to their account
  * We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
  * It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking.

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur we will notify the users via email **** within 1 business day.

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

#### We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

#### To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

** ** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. We will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

3100 Clarendon Blvd., Suite 200  
Arlington, VA 22201  
United States  
202-505-4681
